<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Mobile Coursework 2019</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle"><b>Application Specification</b></string>
    <string name="article_text">
        You are required to implement an Android application described by the specifications below.
        \nYou are not allowed to use third-party libraries. The only libraries you can use are the
        standard Android API libraries found in the following URL:
        \nhttps://developer.android.com/reference/
        \nIt is important to follow exactly the specifications and your implementation must conform to
        these:
        \nThe application developed will be displaying country flags and you should use the images
        found in the following website:
        \nhttps://github.com/hjnilsson/country-flags
        \nThe website provides 256 countries flags images in different resolutions and also a file
        (countries.json) which maps the 2-letter ISO-3166 country code (used in the images filenames
        ) to country names.
        \n\n1. When the application starts, it presents the user with 4 buttons labelled Guess the
        Country,Guess-Hints, Guess the Flag and Advanced Level. (4 marks)
        \n\n2.
        \n(a) Clicking on the Guess the Country button, it should display to the user one random
        flag image picked randomly (and NOT in the same random sequence every time the application
        restarts) from the 256 countries.
        The screen should also display a dropdown list with ALL the names of the 256 countries and a
        button labelled Submit. The user should use the list to select the country that the flag
        corresponds to and clicking the “Submit” button he/she submits the guess to the app.
        (11 marks)
         \n(b) As soon as the user submits the answer, the message CORRECT! (in green colour) or the
        message WRONG! (in red colour) appears on the screen with the name of the correct country in
        Blue colour, depending on whether the answer given is correct or incorrect respectively.
        (4 marks)</string>
</resources>
